<contentList date="7/18/2021 18:00">
    <content contentuid="d45e0ed0-359f-4637-9668-449b48b3c40f" version="1">Arcanist</content>
    <content contentuid="edfd2ae9-d858-4c55-b87b-902d5e0c6da4" version="1">Arcanists are Sorcerous Wizards born with an innate ability to manipulate magic, yet, as studied as a Wizard would be. Rather than focus on the innate abilities of their bloodlines or the research and study of the arcane magic, arcanists use their unique insight into the workings of magic to apply both approaches at once. Their distinct views on magic, extensive knowledge, and tremendous potential often leads them down reckless paths in pursuit of greater powers. Like a wizard, arcanists may call a familiar.</content>
    <content contentuid="39703536-bf7f-467d-9c51-28e7e7ce4a10" version="1">Arcane Bolt I</content>
    <content contentuid="be615c5e-1ef3-4eb5-97c7-824277577ca1" version="1">Provides a class specific cantrip that allows the caster to cast a single bolt of force that also drains life.</content>
    <content contentuid="ce845e86-56b6-419f-a132-f5a8e07151e2" version="1">Arcane Bolt II</content>
    <content contentuid="5b9a8bfa-7830-46c2-b906-f8b3b182cd1e" version="1">Provides a class specific cantrip that allows the caster to cast two bolts of force that also drain life.</content>
    <content contentuid="5c51176a-7a53-4909-8a25-573630cd42a9" version="1">Arcane Bolt III</content>
    <content contentuid="d33148e5-42f1-43ce-831b-1635612a211a" version="1">Provides a class specific cantrip that allows the caster to cast three bolts of force that also drain life.</content>
    <content contentuid="347cb964-4c4d-488a-8c4a-6b2d2754fef5" version="1">Arcane Bolt IV</content>
    <content contentuid="5035e1fd-f161-46a9-a8b2-8003bca06d56" version="1">Provides a class specific cantrip that allows the caster to cast four bolts of force that also drain life.</content>
    <content contentuid="53cdb4dd-f50d-46e2-ad4b-da85ea0645ff" version="1">Ritual Caster</content>
    <content contentuid="3ae55d4c-a794-4bcd-b93c-c0676cd77141" version="1">Ritual casting allows the caster to invoke certain spells without expanding a spell slot.</content>
</contentList>